<odoo>

    <template id="blog_details_template" name="Blog Details Page">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

           <!-- <xpath expr="." position="inside">
                <meta charset="utf-8"/>
                <meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="IE=edge"/>
                <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0, maximum-scale=1.0"/>
                <link rel="shortcut icon" href="favicon.ico" type="image/x-icon"/>
                <title>University of Science &amp; Technology</title>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_home/static/src/css/stylesheet.css" type="text/css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_home/static/src/css/responsive.css" type="text/css"/>

            </xpath>-->
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
                                <div id="wrap">


            <section class="innerBanner newsBanner newsBannerDet bgCover"
                     style="background: url(ust_website_home/static/src/images/news-detail-banner.jpg) no-repeat center right;">
                <div class="container flexBox itemCenter">
                    <div class="innerBannerText">
                        <span class="mb-20">E-learning: Prospects, Challenges, and a Pioneering Experience for the
                            University of
                            Science and Technology
                        </span>
                        <span class="byAdmin">By admin / December 22, 2024</span>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <section class="pt60 pb60">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="blogDetImg">
                        <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-detail.jpg" alt=""/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="blogDetInfo">
                        <u>E-learning</u>
                        has gained great importance due to its many advantages that contribute to supporting the
                        educational process and giving it great flexibility. Due to the rapid technological development,
                        and as a result of the changes caused by the Covid-19 pandemic in terms of direct social
                        communication, the world has witnessed in recent years a major transformation of the e-learning
                        system, helped by the improvement of global communications technology and the availability of
                        the Internet at high speeds.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>E-learning concept</strong>
                        <br/>
                        E - Learning is virtual education over the Internet, using modern technological means, such as:
                        computers, smartphones, and tablets.
                        <br/>
                        <u>E-learning</u>
                        depends on a digital electronic environment, in which technology is employed and technological
                        media are used in communication between the learner and the teacher or educational institution.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Types of e- learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Asynchronous E-Learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        In it, the educational process takes place between students and the teacher at the same time,
                        meaning that learning is direct, which allows interaction between the teacher and students. This
                        type is applied through many means, such as: chat rooms, virtual classrooms, voice calls, and
                        others.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Asynchronous E-Learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        Unlike the previous type, in this type the education process is indirect, as the student and
                        teacher are not required to be present at the same time, as lectures and courses are provided,
                        and the student can access them at the time that suits him, and interaction takes place via
                        electronic discussion forums.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Blended Learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        It is a type that combines synchronous and asynchronous <u>e-learning</u> , and blended learning
                        refers to that type of education that combines traditional education and e-learning.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Advantages of e- Learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Temporal and spatial flexibility</li>
                            <li>E-learning learners can access educational content anytime, anywhere.</li>
                            <li>relatively low cost</li>
                            <li>E-learning is less expensive than traditional education, which requires many costs, such
                                as transportation and travel expenses.
                            </li>
                            <li>Subjectivity and individuality in learning</li>
                            <li>E-learning enhances the self-learning process, and the student's access to study
                                materials on his own when he needs or desires to do so.
                            </li>
                            <li>Multiple and diverse educational media and methods</li>
                            <li>E-learning media vary between video, audio, images, written texts, and digital
                                interactions. Teaching methods also vary, such as explanation in more than one way,
                                direct interaction, and others. These methods can be adapted to suit the student.
                            </li>
                            <li>Achieving equal access to education</li>
                            <li>E-learning is a suitable alternative for individuals who have difficulty receiving
                                education in schools or universities due to geographical, social or economic factors.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Disadvantages and challenges of e- learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Poor social interaction</li>
                            <li>E-learning may lack direct interaction between learners and teachers, as it weakens
                                dialogue, discussion, and the exchange of opinions and ideas between them; this
                                negatively affects the learning experience, as the human factor is absent in the
                                educational process.
                            </li>
                            <li>Technical challenges</li>
                            <li>Despite the technological development that the world is currently witnessing, some
                                regions still suffer from the lack of an appropriate infrastructure for e-learning. Some
                                students may also face problems in using educational platforms, and they will need to
                                develop their technical skills to benefit from e-learning.
                            </li>
                            <li>Low motivation to learn</li>
                            <li>E-learning can cause poor motivation to learn, low levels of enthusiasm, difficulty
                                maintaining self-discipline, increased distraction and poor concentration, and boredom
                                from spending too much time in front of the screen.
                            </li>
                            <li>Difficulties in assessment, quality assurance and academic accreditation</li>
                            <li>E-learning faces several difficulties, including evaluating student performance in the
                                digital environment, ensuring the quality of e-learning content, and the lack or
                                scarcity of sound mechanisms for evaluating and accrediting e-learning programmes.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Fundamentals of improving e- learning</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Developing the digital infrastructure needed for e-learning.</li>
                            <li>Improving the skills of teachers and students in the field of e-learning, and qualifying
                                them for the optimal use of e-learning platforms.
                            </li>
                            <li>Developing and diversifying e-learning content, presenting it in interactive and
                                attractive ways, and linking it to students' needs and goals, ensuring effective
                                learning and achieving educational goals.
                            </li>
                            <li>Evaluation, quality control, linking the evaluation process to educational objectives,
                                as well as linking e-learning to global quality control and accreditation systems.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                        <br/>
                        <div class="flexBox itemCenter blogDetinBox">
                            <div class="img">
                                <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-detial-img2.jpg" alt=""/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="det">
                                <strong>The future of e- learning</strong>
                                <br/>
                                <br/>
                                E-learning is expected to continue to grow and evolve in the coming years, and to gain
                                greater public acceptance.
                                <br/>
                                <br/>
                                E-learning is also expected to undergo several transformations due to the continuous
                                technological development and changes in learning methods.
                                <br/>
                                <br/>
                                Technology is also expected to further improve the learning experience, with AI playing
                                a role in this improvement, especially in personalizing educational content to meet the
                                needs of each individual student.
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>The pioneering experience of the University of Science and Technology in e- learning
                        </strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        In recent years, many universities around the world have turned to the e-learning system, and
                        the Covid-19 pandemic has contributed to universities' trend towards e-learning. <u>The
                        University of Science and Technology
                    </u> is credited with having achieved a precedent in this field, as its move towards e-learning was
                        early, not only locally, as it is the first Yemeni university to enter the e-learning system ,
                        but it was also ahead of many universities regionally and globally, whether in terms of
                        antiquity or precedence in applying modern practices in e-learning. The first seed was
                        represented by the university's establishment of the Affiliation Department in <u>the College of
                        Administrative and Human Sciences
                    </u> in 1994, then the establishment of the Distance Learning Center in 2002, which was transformed
                        in 2008 into a deanship called the Deanship of Open Education and Distance Learning. In 2017,
                        the services provided by the deanship were developed to include e-learning according to regional
                        and international standards, and the name of the deanship was changed to the Deanship of
                        E-Learning and Open Education, to be changed in 2021 <u>to the Deanship of E-Learning and
                        Distance Education</u>.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <u>The University of Science and Technology</u>
                        has provided a distinguished model to be emulated in the field of e-learning, as it has opened
                        many academic specializations that meet the market requirements and students' inclinations,
                        diversified teaching methods and approaches, and provided various services and sources for
                        e-learning, including writing university books according to academic standards and self-learning
                        specifications, providing audio-visual aids, audio, visual, and text lectures, virtual classes,
                        in addition to electronic radio, as well as the educational radio and television production
                        center, and provided a service for live educational meetings between students and teachers.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <u>The University of Science and Technology's</u>
                        experience in this field has expanded to establish an electronic <u>alumni club , an electronic
                        learning system (LMS)
                    </u> between students and supervisors or teachers, as well as an electronic portal system (ISSS)
                        developed entirely internally according to academic and scientific standards. The portal has
                        proven successful in improving and accelerating academic and administrative services, as it
                        contains many services for students, academics and administrators, including an automated
                        academic advisor that guides students in choosing study materials.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        The achievements of <u>the University of Science and Technology</u> in the field of e-learning
                        have contributed to the growth and increase in the number of students enrolled in this type of
                        education. The university's efforts were crowned by obtaining first place among the Arab
                        universities participating in the Creativity and Excellence in Distance Learning Competition,
                        which was held by the Arab Network for Open Education and Distance Learning, headquartered in
                        the Jordanian capital, Amman, in 2011.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        As <u>the University of Science and Technology</u> believes in the loftiness of its educational
                        mission, and is keen to serve the community in various fields, the university has presented
                        several community initiatives within the framework of serving the community in the field of
                        e-learning, including: providing electronic copies in PDF format of authored books, and
                        providing educational resources and materials to those interested by displaying them on the
                        Deanship of E-Learning and Distance Education channel on the YouTube platform, where thousands
                        of visual lectures are available on the channel in the various <u>academic disciplines offered
                        by the university</u>.
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <section class="pb60">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="blogListSlider sliderArrow">
                        <div class="item">
                            <div class="img">
                                <a href="#">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-slider.jpg" alt=""/>
                                </a>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="item">
                            <div class="img">
                                <a href="#">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-slider.jpg" alt=""/>
                                </a>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="item">
                            <div class="img">
                                <a href="#">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-slider.jpg" alt=""/>
                                </a>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="item">
                            <div class="img">
                                <a href="#">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-slider.jpg" alt=""/>
                                </a>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div class="item">
                            <div class="img">
                                <a href="#">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_home/static/src/images/blog-slider.jpg" alt=""/>
                                </a>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="newsDetBot">
                        <div class="prev">
                            <a href="#">
                                <span class="material-icons arrow">chevron_left</span>
                                University of Science and Technology - Aden: 25th place in the Arab world
                            </a>
                        </div>
                        <div class="next">
                            <a href="#">The College of Engineering and Computer Science conducts a field visit to Red
                                Rick Art Production Company
                                <span class="material-icons arrow">chevron_right</span>
                            </a>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
                                </div>

           <!-- <script src="ust_website_home/static/src/js/jquery.min.js"></script>
            <script src="ust_website_home/static/src/js/function.js"></script>
            <script src="ust_website_home/static/src/js/slick.min.js"></script>-->
            <script>
                $('.blogListSlider').slick({
                dots: false,
                speed: 600,
                slidesToShow: 1,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: true,
                autoplay: true,
                });
            </script>

        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>