<odoo>
    <template id="applied_college_template" name="Applied college Page">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

           <!--  <xpath expr="." position="inside">
                <meta charset="utf-8"/>
                <meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="IE=edge"/>
                <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0, maximum-scale=1.0"/>
                <link rel="shortcut icon" href="favicon.ico" type="/ust_website_contactus/static/src/image/x-icon"/>
                <title>University of Science &amp; Technology</title>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/css/slick.css" type="text/css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/css/stylesheet.css" type="text/css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/css/responsive.css" type="text/css"/>
            </xpath>-->

            <div class="oe_structure"/>
            <section class="innerBanner bgCover"
                     style="background: url(/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/images/applied-college-banner.jpg) no-repeat center right;">
                <div class="container flexBox itemCenter">
                    <div class="innerBannerText">
                        <span class="mb-20">Applied
                            <br/>
                            College
                        </span>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <section class="pt60 pb60">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="flexBox">
                        <div class="middleLeft">
                            <ul class="leftTab">
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#AboutCenter" class="scroll2">About The Center</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#Vision" class="scroll2">Vision</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#Message" class="scroll2">Message</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#DeansWord" class="scroll2">Dean's Word</a>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        <div class="middleRight">
                            <div class="pb60" id="AboutCenter">
                                <div class="mainHd">About the Center</div>
                                <div class="textBox mb-20">
                                    <ul class="listText">
                                        <li>Graduating specialized professional cadres who possess the knowledge and
                                            skills that qualify them to compete for employment opportunities locally and
                                            regionally.
                                        </li>
                                        <li>Self-building and promoting positive behaviors for community development.
                                        </li>
                                        <li>Providing government institutions and business organizations with
                                            specialized professional staff.
                                        </li>
                                        <li>Activating partnerships with similar institutions working in the field of
                                            vocational education and relevant local and international organizations.
                                        </li>
                                    </ul>
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <img src="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/images/about-center2.jpg"
                                         alt="About The Center"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="pb60" id="Vision">
                                <div class="mainHd">Vision</div>
                                <div class="textBox mb-20">The College of Applied Science and Technology aspires to be
                                    the leading college at the local and regional levels by offering technical and
                                    professional programs that meet the requirements of the labor market and keep pace
                                    with technological developments.
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <img src="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/images/our-message.jpg" alt="Vision"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="pb60" id="Message">
                                <div class="mainHd">Message</div>
                                <div class="textBox mb-20">The College of Applied Science and Technology seeks to
                                    contribute to meeting the needs of the local and regional market for qualified
                                    professional cadres; through an advanced educational and technical environment, a
                                    competent human cadre, and community service relations in accordance with quality
                                    standards and academic accreditation.
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <img src="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/images/our-vision.jpg" alt="Message"/>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div id="DeansWord">
                                <div class="mainHd">Dean's Word</div>
                                <div class="textBox">
                                    In the name of God, the most gracious, the most merciful
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    It is with great joy, pleasure and happiness that I write these simple words to
                                    announce the opening of the official website of the College of Applied Sciences and
                                    Technology - a private community college - Aden, which includes comprehensive
                                    information about the college in terms of departments, academic programs, study
                                    plans, and the college's vision, mission and goals.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    I am also honored to be the Dean of the College during this period to work within
                                    the College's staff and its wonderful team, which has been the first to translate
                                    the College's vision and mission until they reached this level of distinguished
                                    performance.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    The College of Applied Science and Technology - Aden - strives, through the programs
                                    it offers, to meet the needs of the labor market and contribute to eliminating
                                    unemployment; this is done through:
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    - Choosing modern and advanced educational curricula that keep pace with the
                                    requirements and needs of the labor market in accordance with quality standards and
                                    academic accreditation.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    - Creating an attractive educational environment in light of the current challenges,
                                    by providing a number of technical laboratories equipped with the latest advanced
                                    devices and equipment, necessary for training students on them.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    - Attracting competent educational cadres with high academic qualifications,
                                    distinguished experience and specialization in vocational education in line with
                                    quality requirements and commitment to academic accreditation standards.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    - Continuous development of the capabilities of faculty members and administrative
                                    staff to keep pace with rapid changes in the field of technology, as they are one of
                                    the main pillars and important inputs to the college.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    - Contracting with many public and private hospitals to facilitate the application
                                    and training process for college students within these hospitals.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>
                                    Finally, the College Deanship is fully prepared to receive comments, opinions and
                                    suggestions through this website, and we will consider them an important source for
                                    developing institutional and academic work within the College. God is the Grantor of
                                    success and the Guide to the right path.
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
            <script src="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/js/jquery.min.js"></script>
          <script src="/ust_website_programmes/static/src/js/function.js"></script>
            <script src="/ust_website_applied_college/static/src/js/slick.min.js"></script>
            <script>
                $('.ipSlider').slick({
                dots: false,
                speed: 600,
                slidesToShow: 5,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: true,
                autoplay: true,
                responsive: [
                {
                breakpoint: 1169,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 4,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                {
                breakpoint: 767,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 3,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                {
                breakpoint: 479,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 2,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                ]
                });
                $('.blogList').slick({
                dots: false,
                speed: 600,
                slidesToShow: 4,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: true,
                autoplay: true,
                responsive: [
                {
                breakpoint: 1169,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 3,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                {
                breakpoint: 767,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 2,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                {
                breakpoint: 479,
                settings: {
                slidesToShow: 1,
                slidesToScroll: 1,
                arrows: false,
                }
                },
                ]
                });
            </script>


        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>