<odoo>
    <template id="handramout_branch_details_template" name="Handramout Branch Details Page">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

           <!-- <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/css/slick.css"
                  type="text/css"/>
            <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/css/stylesheet.css"
                  type="text/css"/>
            <link rel="stylesheet" href="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/css/responsive.css"
                  type="text/css"/>-->

            <div class="oe_structure"/>
            <div id="wrap">

                <section class="innerBanner bgCover detail"
                         style="background: url(/ust_website_university_study/static/src/images/hadramout-branch-banner.jpg) no-repeat center right;">
                    <div class="container flexBox itemCenter">
                        <div class="innerBannerText">
                            <span class="mb-20">About Hadramout Branch</span>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section class="detailTabsCon">
                    <div class="container">
                        <ul>
                            <li class="active">
                                <a href="#">College of Medicine and Health Sciences</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <a href="#">College of Engineering and Computer Science</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <a href="#">College of Administrative and Human Sciences</a>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section class="pt60 pb60">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="mainHd">Features of studying at the College of Medicine and Health Sciences</div>
                        <div class="textBox">Students in the College of Medicine and Health Sciences enjoy a wide range
                            of
                            advantages, the most important of which are the availability of infrastructure, specialized
                            professional staff, modern equipment and devices, in addition to the University of Science
                            and
                            Technology's private hospital equipped with specialized professional staff for training. The
                            College of Medicine and Health Sciences affiliated with the University of Science and
                            Technology
                            is also distinguished by being the first medical college in Yemen; This is attributed to a
                            number of factors, the most important of which are: the stimulating educational environment
                            equipped with the latest laboratories, the qualified and experienced teaching staff, and a
                            group
                            of other factors that have led, in their entirety, to the continuation of the development
                            horizon and the adoption of modern patterns for studying medicine and health sciences that
                            keep
                            pace with modern teaching methods.
                        </div>
                        <div class="detailSubTab mb-30">
                            <ul class="flexBox">
                                <li class="active">
                                    <a href="#">Oral and Dental Medicine and Surgery</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#">Pharmacy</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#">Medical Laboratories</a>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <a href="#">Therapeutic Nutrition and Diets</a>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        <div>
                            <div class="mainHd">About The Major</div>
                            <div class="smallTextBox mb-30">
                                The Oral and Dental Medicine and Surgery Program was established in 1994 and is
                                considered
                                one of the first programs at the University of Science and Technology, as the first
                                batch
                                graduated in 1999. The first three batches graduating from the College of Dentistry at
                                the
                                university are considered the first at the level of public and private universities in
                                Yemen.
                                <br/>
                                <br/>
                                The courses included in the program are prepared and implemented according to the
                                quality
                                system adopted by the university in accordance with international quality systems. The
                                program aims primarily to graduate a cadre capable of providing therapeutic and research
                                services in the community, based on the knowledge, skills, and theoretical and practical
                                experiences it has acquired.
                            </div>
                            <div class="flexBox departmentMessage">
                                <div class="img">
                                    <img src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/images/department-message.jpg"
                                         alt=""/>
                                </div>
                                <div class="det">
                                    <div class="mainHd">Department Message</div>
                                    <div class="smallTextBox mb-20">The Bachelor of Therapeutic Nutrition and Dietetics
                                        Program at the College of Medicine and Health Sciences, University of Science
                                        and
                                        Technology, seeks to prepare a cadre with high practical and professional
                                        competencies in the specialty and to contribute to the development of
                                        therapeutic
                                        nutrition research and services in the community through a distinguished
                                        educational
                                        environment and modern curricula with a competent and distinguished academic and
                                        administrative cadre using the latest modern educational methods in accordance
                                        with
                                        quality standards and academic accreditation.
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="mb-20 largeFont">
                                        <span>Competitive test materials</span>
                                        (Biology - Chemistry - English).
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="mb-20 grayBg boxContent">
                                        <span class="hd">Vision</span>
                                        <div class="smallTextBox">Leadership and excellence locally and regionally in
                                            teaching therapeutic nutrition and diets.
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="grayBg boxContent">
                                        <span class="hd">Information about the major</span>
                                        <ul class="smallTextBox">
                                            <li>Academic degree: Bachelor's degree</li>
                                            <li>Duration of study: 4 years</li>
                                            <li>Language of instruction: Arabic for required subjects and English for
                                                specialized subjects
                                            </li>
                                            <li>Type of secondary school: Scientific</li>
                                            <li>Secondary school average: 70%</li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="pt60">
                                <div class="branchBox">
                                    <div class="flexBox programObjectives">
                                        <div class="det">
                                            <div class="mainHd">Program Objectives</div>
                                            <ul class="listText small">
                                                <li>Providing students with various professional knowledge and skills in
                                                    the
                                                    field of therapeutic nutrition and diets in response to the
                                                    requirements
                                                    of society and the labor market.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>Preparing highly qualified cadres in the field of therapeutic
                                                    nutrition
                                                    and diets.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>To enhance students' thinking and problem-solving skills through
                                                    research and effective communication, enabling them to deal with
                                                    various
                                                    nutritional issues.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>Providing a teaching and learning environment that keeps pace with
                                                    professional and technological progress.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>Strengthening the relationship with all parties related to the
                                                    specialty.
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class="img">
                                            <img src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/images/program-objectives.jpg"
                                                 alt=""/>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="conditionBox">
                                        <div class="mainHd">Conditions for admission and registration in the Therapeutic
                                            Nutrition and Diets Program
                                        </div>
                                        <ul class="flexBox conditionList">
                                            <li>
                                                <div class="inner">
                                                    <span class="count">01</span>
                                                    Holders of a high school diploma from the Republic of Yemen, or its
                                                    equivalent, are accepted into the specialization, with the average
                                                    determined annually by the Ministry of Higher Education and
                                                    Scientific
                                                    Research.
                                                </div>
                                            </li>
                                            <li>
                                                <div class="inner">
                                                    <span class="count">02</span>
                                                    Submit all required documents certified with the university
                                                    admission
                                                    application to the Admissions and Registration Department.
                                                </div>
                                            </li>
                                            <li>
                                                <div class="inner">
                                                    <span class="count">03</span>
                                                    Admission is based on the university's capacity and approved by the
                                                    Ministry of Higher Education and Scientific Research.
                                                </div>
                                            </li>
                                            <li>
                                                <div class="inner">
                                                    <span class="count">04</span>
                                                    The student undertakes to abide by the university's regulations,
                                                    instructions and rules in effect during the study period.
                                                </div>
                                            </li>
                                            <li>
                                                <div class="inner">
                                                    <span class="count">05</span>
                                                    Students enrolled in some college programs are subject to
                                                    competitive
                                                    tests, which are a criterion for admission to the college. This is
                                                    done
                                                    through determining the level, a personal interview, as well as
                                                    competition in the average and the admission test.
                                                </div>
                                            </li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="pt60">
                                <div class="flexBox departmentMessage">
                                    <div class="img">
                                        <img src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/images/high-school-graduates.jpg"
                                             alt=""/>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="det">
                                        <div class="mainHd">Documents required for high school graduates:</div>
                                        <ul class="countList small mb-20">
                                            <li>Application form (admission) with all the information included in it,
                                                according to the university's conditions.
                                            </li>
                                            <li>Original certified high school transcript or equivalent, with a
                                                certified
                                                copy attached.
                                            </li>
                                            <li>If the secondary school is from outside Yemen, it must be certified
                                                (original + copy) by the following authorities:
                                                <ul class="listText small">
                                                    <li>The Ministry of Education in the country that issued the
                                                        certificate.
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li>The Ministry of Foreign Affairs of the country issuing the
                                                        certificate.
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li>Its equivalence in the Yemeni Ministry of Education.</li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <div class="largeFont">
                                            <span>If the high school certificate is from a non-Arab country, it will be
                                                translated after being certified and the translated copy certified
                                                (according to paragraph No. 3 above), in addition to its equivalence at
                                                the
                                                Ministry of Education in the Republic of Yemen.
                                            </span>
                                        </div>
                                        <ul class="countList small">
                                            <li>A copy of the personal or family card for Yemeni students.</li>
                                            <li>Six personal photos, size (4x6) with a white background.</li>
                                            <li>Photos of the first eight pages of the passport (for non-Yemenis),
                                                provided
                                                that the passport is valid for more than one year and indicates
                                                residence in
                                                Yemen for at least one year.
                                            </li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <div class="oe_structure"/>

                <script src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/js/jquery.min.js"></script>
                <script src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/js/function.js"></script>
                <script src="/ust_website_university_study/static/src/js/slick.min.js"></script>
                <script>
                    $('.campusSlider').slick({
                    dots: true,
                    speed: 400,
                    slidesToShow: 1,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    autoplay: true,
                    autoplaySpeed: 8000,
                    cssEase: 'linear'
                    });

                    $('.actvitySlider').slick({
                    dots: false,
                    speed: 600,
                    slidesToShow: 3,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: true,
                    autoplay: true,
                    responsive: [
                    {
                    breakpoint: 1169,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 3,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    {
                    breakpoint: 767,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 2,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    {
                    breakpoint: 479,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 2,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    ]
                    });
                    $('.blogList').slick({
                    dots: false,
                    speed: 600,
                    slidesToShow: 4,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: true,
                    autoplay: true,
                    responsive: [
                    {
                    breakpoint: 1169,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 3,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    {
                    breakpoint: 767,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 2,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    {
                    breakpoint: 479,
                    settings: {
                    slidesToShow: 1,
                    slidesToScroll: 1,
                    arrows: false,
                    }
                    },
                    ]
                    });
                </script>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>